by RentAnAdviser.com
Pack yourself a toothbrush dear
Pack yourself a favorite blouse
Take a withdrawal slip, take
all of your savings out
Cause if we don't leave this town
We might never make it out
I was not born to drown, baby come on
Forget what Father Brennan said
We were not born in sin
Leave a note on your bed
Let your mother know you're safe
And by the time she wakes
We'll have driven through the state
We'll have driven through
the night, baby come on
If the sun don't shine on me today
And if the subways flood
and bridges break
Will you lay yourself down
and dig your grave
Or will you rail against
your dying day
And when we looked outside,
couldn't even see the sky
How do you pay the rent,
is it your parents
Or is it hard work dear
Holding the atmosphere
I don't wanna live like that
If the sun don't shine on me today
If the subways flood and
the bridges break
Jesus Christ can't save me tonight
Put on your dress, yes
wear something nice
Decide on me, yea decide on us
Oh, oh, oh, Illinois, Illinois
Pack yourself a toothbrush dear
Pack yourself a favorite blouse
Take a withdrawal slip, take
all of your savings out
Cause if we don't leave this town
We might never make it out
by RentAnAdviser.com